	╔═══════════════════════════╗
	║	 Map Editor 1.0	               ║
	╠═══════════════════════════╣
	║ Author:    Andrea Cammarata             ║
	╚═══════════════════════════╝
	
╔═══════════════╗
║ About the program   ║
╚═══════════════╝
With this program created by me with Truevision 3D engine and DirectX 8, is possibile generate a 3D map very easy.
In this version of the program, because i will do another with Save function, mirror, etc, you can build a 3D map
simply using the relative buttons for add Walls, Floors, Ceiling , Trasparent Wall - Floors - Ceilings with
multy color corner, False Reflection Walls - Floors - Ceilings and finally is possibile load
.X / .3ds files in the map and move it, scale it and rotate it all in real time.
The programs support at the moment two lenguage:
- English
- Italian
and some function like Zoom, Map Scale impostation, etc.
Enjoy the programs and if you like it, vote me ; ).

╔═══════════════╗
║        Commands        ║
╚═══════════════╝
- For add a wall you must:
  1) Click the right mouse button for the start point of the wall
  2) Click the left mouse button for the end point of the wall

- For add a floor or celing you must click the mouse button in the followin order:

		( Right button )                            ( Left button )
			1  --------------------------------------- 2
			   |                                       |
                                                   |                                       |
                                                   |                                       |
                                                   |                                       |
                                                   |                                       |
                                                   |                                       |
                                               	3  --------------------------------------- 4
                                 ( Right button )                            ( Left Button )


- Press Canc to remove a wall, floor or ceiling under construction
- If the space is not enought in the editor, press S Key on the keyboard and simoultanely the
  left mouse button and move the mouse in one direction,
  With this trick you can scroll the map.
- In 3D modality preview hit the direction key to move and move the mouse up for look up, down to look down,etc
╔═══════════════╗
║        Contact              ║
╚═══════════════╝
For any question, please mail to:
       
                                             Spike84@inwind.it